NIKITA POPOV

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER (REACT, VUE.JS, LARAVEL)



Download PDF

CONTACTS

Yerevan, Armenia 💿

+7-964-364-85-64

@nikitos_only_one

tomkitos_omy_one

nikitos.one@gmail.com

github.com/nikitos-one

linkedin.com/in/nikitos-one in

PROFILE

Hi, I am a Fullstack developer with 5+ years of experience in development new features and apps of different levels of complexity. I have worked with two main frontend frameworks (React, Vue.js). I am also interested in a deeper study of backend technologies, so I am improving my skills in this area (PHP, Laravel, NodeJS, MySQL, PostgreSQL, RestAPI, GraphQL).

Now I am looking for a company that develops interesting products and uses modern technologies, where I can apply my knowledge and experience, join a friendly development team.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree / Information Technology

Stavropol College of Communications Stavropol, Russia

2007 - 2011

Master's degree /

Information Technology

Stavropol State Agrarian University
Stavropol, Russia
2012 - 2016 (not finished)

Bachelor's degree /

Lawyer

North Caucasian Social Institute Stavropol, Russia 2012 - 2016

SKILLS

My tech stacks:

JavaScript/TypeScript: **React** (Redux, MobX, Hook, React Router),**Vue.js** (VueX, Vue Router, NuxtJS, Axios, Composition API)

PHP: Laravel, WordPress, OpenCart, Bitrix CMS, Simpla CMS, Slim Framework

UI/UX:

HTML/CSS, HTML5/CSS3, SCSS/SASS, styled-components, Bootstrap, Vuetify

Database:

MySQL, MSSQL, PostgreSQL

Development Tools:

Webpack, Docker, Github, Gitlab, Figma, Adobe Photoshop/Illustrator

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Developer (Laravel, Bitrix CMS, WordPress, React, Vue.js)

Ladoga Group (Ltd "Compass") | Saint-Petersburg, Russia | Apr. 2021 - Present

- Development and implementation of a CRM system.
- Development and maintenance of an online store.
- Creation of promo sites and information resources.

Fullstack Developer (Laravel, Vue.js)

JSC "RIVC-Pulkovo" | Saint-Petersburg, Russia | Oct. 2019 - Feb. 2021

- Maintenance of the system of automation of air transport processes.
- Development and implementation of new functionality.
- Integration with various information systems and services.

Head of IT department (Opencart, WordPress, Vue.js, JQuery, JavaScript)

Ltd "Technoenergo" | Stavropol, Russia | Apr. 2018 - Mar. 2019

- Organization of the work of the IT structure of the enterprise.
- Selection and purchase of the necessary equipment.
- Development and control over the maintenance of an online store.
- Setting up cash equipment, integration with payment and other systems.

Fullstack Developer (Simpla CMS, JQuery, JavaScript)

Leadersport (Self employed) | Stavropol, Russia | July. 2017 - Mar. 2018

- Development and maintenance of an online store.
- Integration with payment and other systems.

System Administrator (Windows, Linux file systems, MSSQL Server, Synology, Cisco)

Ltd "YugStroyInvest" | Stavropol, Russia | Jan. 2017 - June. 2017

- Administration of Linux, Windows workstations and network equipment.
- Administration of the file server, MSSQL server and accounting services.

Fullstack Developer (WordPress, JQuery, JavaScript)

Ltd "Sphere" | Stavropol, Russia | Apr. 2016 - Sept. 2016

• Creation of promo sites and information resources.

Commissioner for combating computer crimes

State organization | Stavropol, Russia | Mar. 2013 - Feb. 2016

• Suppression of crimes in the field of information technology: illegal access to computer information" (fishing, carding, skimming, DDos attacks, etc.)